at icici lombard we not only keep our
promise of meeting customer needs
but also go beyond their expectations
by hand holding them in their are of
need
but seamless claim settlement and full
support
[Music]
one of our long-standing customers who
endorses
our customer-centric approach in an
unfortunate turn of events
they suffered an extensive damage of 243
million rupees
due to a massive fire at the factory
india under lockdown
strict restrictions on entry in daman
initiating the claim process was an
uphill task
[Music]
the odds were stacked against us
so we innovated
live aerial videography using a drone
to a certain overall damage
hello it
to stand is our customers when they're
in despair in fact
that is the moment of truth for all of
us
amid the lockdown we used our
technological progress
to ascertain the claim by use of drone
technology
so that at first place we know what is
the total losses and from there on
our team worked with lot of rigor to
settle the claim
[Music]
reserve creation of 225 million
on a short notice for us at isis lombard
the customer comes first
demonstrating situational readiness our
team created a reserve within no time
this immediate response made a big
difference to the customer
as help and support was forthcoming
immediately
special permission from the government
investigation lab of suva
to collect samples from the site
[Music]
as they say when you're committed to
doing good things fall in place and team
isaiah lombard took special permission
to get the samples and shifted from
daman to mumbai
and with timely actions and quick
decisions isis lombard kept the promise
of customer first
thanks team isis lumbar all the best
collection of tally data and other
documents
digitally via a cloud account
i got a call from one of my clients
morning 4 am
and he informed me that one of the units
got good of fire and the entire factory
got engulfed in fire
so it was a major loss the other thought
which i cracked in my mind was
how will i handle the entire uh clay
especially the
postponed lockdown scenario as this
particular factory was also in a green
zone area
and the other vicinities were redrawn so
entry and access was also restricted
but thanks to icici lombard's train team
we were guided on the entire process of
clean documentation
survey was done within 24 hours and
ensured all the document flow happened
within about two months kudos to the
team at icsc lombard
proud to be associated with isis
announced an early interim relief for 50
million rupees
to reduce ensured financial stress
during covet crisis
in the first week of april one of our
factories burned down unfortunately
nothing was left
with covet lockdown and the fire i was
very worried because of the financial
crisis you would be in
that's where icici helped us believe me
icici
has delivered its promise they have
completed all the verifications
validations in the quickest possible
time
and i've been able to arrange an interim
payment to us honestly even i did not
expect the payment to be received so
soon
as i've received this interventionally
i'm looking forward to start my business
again very soon
they've helped me out again and they
made me happy
that i can trust them looking forward
for a longer relationship with them for
the future
when the going gets tough rcici lombard
will
always step up it is a promise
icici lumbar nepali